

MAKSIM MIRZINSKIJ

PROFILE

I am a young, software developer with marketing and project management background. I can do both, develop applications with the help of various IDE's and be part of a project management team.

Furthermore, I have a significant range of skills that can contribute an IT based businesses. Through my education and work experience, I worked out a habit to be curious in all sorts of IT advances.

I am quite passionate in developing my technical skills. Global Business Engineering education have allowed me to be part of numerous projects that I as an IT analyst had to provide solutions, both reflecting business and technical aspects Finally, I am very motivated in career and experience growth. Have ambitions and am not afraid of hard work. Honest in what I do and how I approach specific tasks.

You can check my projects on my portfolio page.

INTEREST













EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER AT ONLY-BESTSELLER

Brief employment at Bestseller, as a frontend developer. Unfortunately, due to corona virus layoffs was part of the released employees.

2014 - 2018

WEBSITE DEVELOPER AT OPENUSOURCE

Have been working with website development using Drupal CMS. Mainly, participated in backend development. At the company, I have improved my programming skills and learned to work in a professional environment. Additionally, in such a small company communication played a significant role.

- Web Development
- Professional IT environment
- Communication Skills

2010 - 2016

MANUAL LABOR/TEAM LEADER AT DANSK SUPERMARKED

I have worked in a warehouse where I was involved with logistics and manual labor. During my six years of hard work, I have managed to become a team leader. This work has helped me to improve my skills in becoming a goal-oriented manager and disciplined me in dealing with adversities.

- Management Skills
- Hard Work
- Ambition

EDUCATION

2014 - 2019

B.ENG., GLOBAL BUSINESS ENGINEERING, VIA UNIVERSITY

The degree qualifies me to fill managerial positions within design and implementation of technical solutions, as well as within marketing and sales.

During the program I have participated in several projects that dealt with finances, marketing and both web and software product developments. Bachelor thesis was based on UX implementation in software development.

1997 - 2009

HIGH SCHOOL, "ZALIAKALNIO" GYMNASIUM



MAKSIM MIRZINSKIJ

SKILLS JavaScript HTML/CSS .Net/C# Java SQL SKILLS English Russian Lithuanian Danish CONTACTS

+45 42213117

maximmirzinskij@gmail.com

Horsens, Nørrebrogade 70, 1 th.

IT SKILLS

In terms of programming, I have work experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript (Node.js, React, Redux), Java, SQL, C#, ASP.NET, WPF.

Capable of working with ERP system: SAP ABAP/4 Programming.

Furthermore, accustomed with such IDE's: Android Studio, Visual Studio and Eclipse.

Have studied and worked with Oracle, Mongo and Neo4j databases.

Plus, I have a good understanding of Software Engineering techniques (Activity, ER, Use Case diagrams and etc.)

Daily user of the Office programs like Word, Excel, Project and PowerPoint.

LANGUAGE SKILLS —

Can write and speak fluently Russian, English and Lithuanian. Currently, going to Danish courses at SprogCenter, Horsens.

LEISURE

In my free time, I like being active and involved in various sport activities. For the last 5 years I have practiced Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu. With its help I became humbler and more disciplined. I also, gained a lot of Danish friends who could help me out with my danish language.

What is more, I have participated in 5 km and 10 km DHL company runs. This experience gave me an understanding of how beneficial such activities can be, for team-bonding. I Hope, that at some point I can be part of Copenhagen's marathon run.

Finally, last year I have discovered diving and managed to become a certified diver. Underwater world fascinates me, I hope that I will continue exploring deep waters, in future.

In addition, in between my sport activities and studies I like to play guitar and read historic and scientific literature.

٠